<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LocalKart</string>
    <string name="home_titlebar">LocalKart <sup><small><small><small>TM</small></small></small></sup></string>

    <string name="progresstitle">Loading... Please Wait</string>
    <string name="somethingwentwrong">Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="nointernet">Check your Network Connection</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="logout_title">Logout</string>
    <string name="logout_msg">Are you sure ?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <string name="internal_storage">Internal storage</string>

    <string name="view_map"><u>View Map</u></string>

    <string name="sup"><sup>₹ </sup></string>

    <string name="user_benefit_1">The user will get a discount of</string>
    <string name="user_benefit_2">when he uses your code while subscribing to a new plan. The user needs to enter and apply the code on the payment page.</string>

    <string name="user_benefit">
        \n<b>User Benefits</b>\nThe user will get discount when he uses your code while subscribing to a new plan. The user needs to enter and apply the code on the payment page.
    </string>
    <string name="your_benefit">
        \n<b>Your Benefits</b>\nWhen a user completes the subscription purchase by using your referral (coupon) code, then you will get the following free benefits which includes additional Daily, Weekly, and Festival Posts along with validity.
    </string>
    <string name="your_benefits">
        \n<b>Your Benefits</b>\nWhen a user completes the subscription purchase by using your referral (coupon) code, then you will get the following free benefits.\n
    </string>
    <string name="note">\n<b>Note</b>
\n1. You can not use your own referral (coupon) code.
\n2. You can send referral (coupon) code to any number of persons.
\n3. An user can redeem the referral (coupon) code only once (for one successful plan subscription).
\n4. However, if you want to enjoy the free benefits, you can send your referral (coupon) code to as many persons as you can.
\n5. The free benefits will be added to you every time when a user buys any subscription plan using your referral (coupon) code.
    \n6. All the free benefits will be canceled when you are upgrading to a higher subscription plan.</string>

    <string name="user_t_c">I agree all <u>Terms and Conditions.</u></string>
    <string name="view_plans"><u>View Plans and Subscribe</u></string>
    <string name="report_post"><u>Report This Post</u></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Rs">\u20B9</string>
</resources>